cafe.com 2019-10-16

# Privacy - CAFE

## Privacy

We are strongly committed to letting you know how we will collect and use your personal information. The policies below are applicable to data and information collected through cafe.com, the affiliated network of websites (including any versions optimized for viewing on a wireless or tablet device); all email newsletters published or distributed by Some Spider, LLC (collectively “Some Spider” or “we,” “us,” or “our”); all apps published by Some Spider; and all other interactive features, services, and communications provided by Some Spider (“Service” or “Services”), however accessed and/or used, that are operated by us, made available by us, or produced and maintained by Some Spider. We have established this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather during your use of this Service, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, and how you can manage your personal information.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered online through our Service. It does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline or by companies or organizations to which we may link or who may link to us.

By using our Service, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Service. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Service following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this Privacy Policy retroactively or to personal information already in our possession, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or don’t see your concerns addressed here, you should contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

What Information About Me Is Collected and Stored?

We collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Service: personal information and non-personal information. Personal information is information that you may supply to us, as described more fully below, i.e., when you register on the Service, upload content, participate in a community, or provide your e-mail address. Personal information is any information that can individually identify you and includes, among other things, your name, e-mail address, telephone number, postal address, and contact information. Non-personal information includes information that does not personally identify you, but it may include tracking and usage information about your location, demographics, use of the Service and the Internet.

Personal Information

As a general matter, you can browse the Service without submitting your personal information to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may supply us with your personal information. The following lists the most common ways in which we may collect your personal information.

  * Registration for an account on the Service
  * Profile information that You provide for Your user profile
  * Sign up to receive alerts, deals, offers or other information via email from Some Spider
  * Service related communications, e.g. account verification; technical notification
  * Participation in communities, chat rooms and comment threads, other fora, and other interactive services like creating a collection of stories on the Service
  * Submission of content or other data and information on any part of the Service that permits it
  * Any other place on the Service where you knowingly volunteer personal information

Non-Personal Information

In addition, when you interact with the Service, we may collect certain information that does not identify you individually and our servers may automatically keep an activity log of your use of our Service (“Non-Personal Information”). Generally, we collect and store the following categories of Non-Personal Information:

  * Non-identifiable demographic data such as age, gender, and five digit zip code as part of collecting personal information
  * Device information about your computer, browser, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Service. This information may include IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language, and other transactional information.
  * Analytics and usage information about your use of the Service.
  * Additional “traffic data” and log files such as time of access, date of access, software crash reports, session identification number, access times, and referring website addresses.
  * Other information regarding your use of the Service.

Collection of Your Source IP Address

We collect and store your device’s source IP address which may disclose the location of your device at the time you access the Service. We may also collect and store other location information about you and associated with your account.

Collection of Personal Information From or Through Social Media Sites or Using Your Social Media Login

When you interact with any Some Spider page or account on a social media platform, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, Reddit, Instagram, or Pinterest, we may collect the personal information that you make available to us on that page or account including your account ID or “handle.” However, we will comply with the privacy policies of the corresponding social media platform and we will only collect and store such personal information that we are permitted to collect by these social media platforms.

Collection of Personal and Non-Personal Information From Other Sources

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources (including by us from our offline interactions with you) to, among other things, enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to better customize your experience on the Service.

Use of Cookies, HTML5 LocalStorage, and Unique URLs

Like many websites, we use “cookies”, which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment and HTML5 LocalStorage, which allows a website to store and retrieve data on your computer and equipment, when you visit certain online pages that record your preferences and actions. We may also use cookies and local storage to monitor traffic, improve the Sites and make it easier and/or relevant for your use. We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. We use cookies and local storage for the other purposes set out below:

  * We use cookies and/or local storage to remind us who you are and to find your account information in our database when you access a service so you do not need to log in at every visit. This helps us to provide you with service tailored to your specific needs and interests. A cookie or other technology is created when you visit the site.
  * We use cookies and/or local storage to determine the browser you use so the site can be designed to work properly with the most common versions of different browsers.
  * Advertisers that place ads on the Sites may use cookies and/or local storage.
  * We use cookies and/or local storage to estimate our audience size. Your browser is given a unique cookie or other technology that helps us determine whether yours is a repeat visit or a first visit.
  * We use cookies and/or local storage to help personalize the Service for you.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies through your browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your web browser to decline cookies, some features of the Sites may not work or may not work as designed. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allabout/).

We also use unique website URLs to track your use of the Services and how you share information you find on the Services. We may link this information with your email address. We use this information to help us improve the Services and the type of content we make available on the Services.

Some Spider works with a variety of advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers and analytics companies. These parties use various technologies, and technologies from third-party companies, to collect data in order to send and serve relevant advertising to users. These technologies may include the placement of cookies or web beacons, the use of HTML5 LocalStorage, the use of unique or non-unique non-personal identifiers and other technologies. These technologies may be used to track user behavior and serve you more relevant advertising. This relevant advertising may appear on our Sites or other websites that you visit. This privacy policy does not cover the use of various technologies by advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies. These companies may also obtain information from services you use from other companies, including without limitation, other websites, mobile websites, mobile downloadable applications, and downloadable applications, and combine that information with information they obtain through these third party technologies on our Services. You should be aware that Some Spider does not have control over these third party technologies or the information contained in them. You should be aware that if you choose to opt out through other sites, this does not opt you out of being served advertising. The ads will just not be targeted to you by any party from which you have opted out. You can also opt out of future information collection from our Services by ceasing use of the Service.

Is Personal Information Collected From Children?

Some Spider does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 16 years of age. If you are under 16 years of age you should not provide personally identifiable information to Some Spider without providing us with consent from your parents. If Some Spider discovers that a child under the age of 16 has provided Some Spider with personally identifiable information and we do not have parental consent, Some Spider will immediately delete that child’s information from the Service.

How Do We Use Your Information?

We use the information we learn from you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Service. We may use your Personal and Non-Personal Information in the following ways:

General Uses

  * Upload your content to our Service as you request
  * Communicate with you about your account (including service related announcements) and send you information about features and enhancements on our Service
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies
  * Communicate with you about your collection or stories or your comment to a community
  * Communicate with you about third party deals and offers
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Service, including providing you reports, recommendations and feedback based on your preferences
  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations
  * Detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Service

Use of Your Location Information

Specifically, we use your location information to:

  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations
  * Detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Service

Combination of Your Personal Information

We use the information from one portion of the Sites on other portions of Sites in our network of Sites or in reports and analysis, all of which are owned and operated by Some Spider, and we may combine information gathered from multiple portions of the Sites into a single customer record or analysis or report.

Who Do We Provide Your Information To?

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose information about your personal information collected online to any companies not part of Some Spider or its subsidiaries or related entities. In no event will we sell or rent your personal information as part of a customer list or similar transaction.

Business Partners and Third Parties

We may share your personal information with our business partners or co-marketers from time to time. Although our treatment of your personal information is governed by this Privacy Policy, the business partner or third party’s treatment of your personal information will be governed by the business partner or third party’s privacy policy.

Third-Party Agents

We have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, such as hosting, email and communication management, storage, content management tools, analytics, customer service, etc. These entities have access to the personal information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personal information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Service.

Emergency Situations

We may also use or disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Service; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Service or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Service or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

Some Spider E-mail Communications

E-mail communications sent from Some Spider or through Some Spider are designed to make your Some Spider experience more efficient or to provide you with information, offers, and deals that we think may be relevant. By participating in the Services, you specifically agree to accept and consent to receiving e-mail communications initiated from Some Spider or through Some Spider. If you do not wish to receive any of our e-mail communications, please do not use the Services.

What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?

We are concerned about ensuring the security of your personal information. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your device to our servers. Personal information collected by our Service are stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose your personal information to you. Please understand, however, that while we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

How Can We Transfer Your Personal Information?

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Some Spider, its affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Some Spider, its affiliates, or service providers may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the United States or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from US law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. By registering for and using the Service you consent to the transfer of information to the US or to any other country in which Some Spider, its affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

How Long Do We Keep Your Information?

Following termination or deactivation of your account, Some Spider, its affiliates, or its service providers may retain information (including your profile information) and user content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes. If you have any questions about termination or deactivation of your account, please contact us directly at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

What Happens When I Link To or From Another Website?

This Service may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy for Some Spider do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other websites.

Governing Law

This Service is published in the United States. We attempt to protect the personal information of all users of our Service and we attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to the Some Spider services, but our Service is located and targeted to United States citizens and our policies are directed at compliance with those laws. If you are uncertain whether this privacy policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to Some Spider.

Assignment

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Service. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Service. As a result, please be aware that in such event we may transfer some or all of your information to a company acquiring all or part of our assets or to another company with which we have merged. Under such circumstances we would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. Nevertheless, we cannot promise that an acquiring company or the merged company will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy.

Changes to This Policy

As our Service continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Service. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use our Service in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy. We will not, however, materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information we have previously collected from you without your express consent.

How Do I Opt-Out or Correct Information About Me

You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters from Some Spider. To opt-out, you can send us a message at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please note, however, that you generally cannot opt-out of Service related announcements, e.g. if the Service is temporarily suspended or if delivery of a product or service is delayed.

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Some Spider who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) These Services will respect your browser’s Do Not Track signals (or other well-established, commercially available mechanisms that provide you with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information). If we receive a Do Not Track notice, we will stop using any personal information for online behavioral advertising purposes.
